Are you trying to prove yourself my equal?
（青峰(あおみね)）
オレとタメはるつもりかよ？
（青峰）けど オマエにゃ 無理だ
You can't do it.
Your light is too dim!
オマエの光じゃ 淡すぎだってよ！
I don't want to lose anymore.
（火神(かがみ)）
嫌なんだよ… もう負けるのは
I'm sick of
嫌なんだよ
泣いてる仲間を見るのは…！
seeing my friends cry!
If I can't do it now,
ここでやらなきゃ
いつやるんだよ！！
when will I do it?!
shoudou ga atte usoppachi ni idonde
I've got the urge to challenge these bold-faced lies.
boku to kimi to ga shujinkou Love song
You and I are the stars of this love song.
dondon ikimashou
It's time to pick up the pace
Translation Checking: AMS
tsuyoki de semeraretanda
before I lose out to some go-getter,
nakamauchi no warai banashi de wa
and end up like the guys my friends joke about.
Editing: AMS
monmon toshitenda ze
It's starting to drive me crazy...
jibun no heya itsu datte
Always cooped up in my room.
Timing: Govna
honto wa yowaki na peach mind
The truth is, I've got a timid peach mind
K-Timing: Eternal Blizzard
ki no aru soburi ka
Does she have a thing for me?
Typesetting: AMS, KmE
Karaoke: KmE
tada no omoikomi ka
Or am I reading too much into it?
baretenda ano ko ni wa
Either way, that girl's got us all figured out.
ganbare otoko no ko
Do your best, boys.
Encoding: Your Mom
kono mama ja sanjuugo renpai
If this keeps up, it'll be 35 straight losses.
kimi dake no boku wa Go to guy
But just for you, I'll be your go-to guy.
he
n
ge
ji
za
i
no
ma
ji
ka
ru
su
ta
a
Phantasmagoric magical star
i
da
na
ru
ma
n
ne
ri
da
t
te
i
ja
na
i
What's wrong with a tried-and-true stereotype?
to
me
ro
a
o
sa
wo
Own up to your own inexperience.
ma
da
mi
chi
nu
ko
i
na
ra
ba
If your love has yet to come full circle,
ze
n
bu
a
ge
ru
ze
I'll give you my all.
ki
mi
ni
chi
ka
u
This I swear to you.
saizen-fansubs.com
Episode
I Won't Lose
（今吉(いまよし)）なっ…
（火神）ふっ！
（桜井(さくらい)）あっ！
（日向(ひゅうが)）あっ…
（桜井）んっ！
This game...
（今吉）これが…
Is this what happens when two guys in the Zone clash?
ゾーンに入ったもん同士が
ぶつかりあうと… こうなるんか
Out of bounds!
（審判）アウト･オブ･バウンズ！
黒ボール！
Black ball!
（リコ）何て戦いなの…
What an unbelievable battle.
Those two are in a completely different dimension.
あの２人だけ
完全に次元が違う…
（小金井(こがねい)）
もう１分近く 点が入ってない…
No one's scored for almost a minute.
What's going to happen now?
（土田(つちだ)）
どうなっちまうんだ これは
Because they're both in the Zone,
（赤司(あかし)）２人とも
ゾーンに入ったことにより—
集中力と反射速度が
最高を超えている
their focus and reaction speed have exceeded their maximums.
Neither one is making any progress.
（氷室(ひむろ)）ラチがあかないな
But why are both teams completely relying on their aces?
（高尾(たかお)）それでも両チーム
エース一辺倒なのはどうなんだ？
If they passed the ball around to
the other four players, couldn't they score?
他の４人でボールを回せば
点 取れるんじゃないのか？
It's pointless.
（緑間(みどりま)）ムダなのだよ
（高尾）ん？
It wouldn't change the outcome.
恐らく結果は変わらない
The Zone doesn't simply allow one
to exhibit 100% of his strength.
ゾーンは
ただ１００％の力を—
発揮するだけの
ものではない
All unnecessary information is cut.
不必要な情報はすべてカットする
His ability to handle necessary information regarding
その分 目の前の相手だけでなく
他の選手の位置や動きなど—
not only the player in front of him,
but also the positions and movements
of the other players increases.
必要な情報の処理能力が向上する
What?
要は“視野が広がる”のだよ
In other words, his field of view widens.
Furthermore, one is the fastest high school student,
加えて 片や
高校最速の男と—
and the other is the highest jumper.
片や高校最高の男だ
守備範囲は 常人のそれを
はるかに超えている
They are far beyond the range of
an ordinary person's defense.
（笠松(かさまつ)）今の２人の前で
生半可な攻めは 逆に危険だ
Against those two, a half-hearted
attack would actually be dangerous.
That's why the game has been left up to the two aces.
だからこそ勝負の行方は
２人のエースに託された
（黄瀬(きせ)）
そんな場面で… いや—
In this situation, how can they...
No, they're doing it because they're in this situation.
そんな場面だからこそっスか
Aomine...
（さつき）青峰君
He's always been like that.
（さつき）昔からそうだった
Since he started playing street ball,
ストリートで
バスケを始めた時から—
the stronger his opponent,
相手が強ければ強いほど—
the more excitement and focus he played with.
目を輝かせて
夢中でプレーしてた
楽しそう…
He looks like he's having fun.
Aomine and Kagami...
青峰君と 火神君
The sparks the two aces sent flying
captivated the entire stadium.
２人のエースが散らす火花は—
会場すべてを魅了し
永遠に続くかに見え—
It seemed to continue endlessly,
and everyone wished it would.
また 誰もが
そうあってほしいとさえ思った
However, the conclusion was sudden.
だけど 決着は突然…
（原澤(はらさわ)）あっ！
（火神）フッ！
（諏佐(すさ)）はっ…！
He passed him!
（降旗(ふりはた)）ぶち抜いたぁ！！
うおおお 火神ぃ！
Kagami!
Seirin
Touou
We're only three points behind now!
Seirin
Touou
（土田）これで３点差だ！
（ホイッスル）
Seirin
Touou
You must be joking.
（今吉）
バカな 火神のほうが速いやと？
Is Kagami faster? What's going on?
どうなっとるんや…
He can't pass him?
（桜井）抜けない…！？
No! There's no way Kagami's faster!
（今吉）違う！ 火神のほうが
速いわけやない！
It must be
これはゾーンのタイムリミット！
the Zone's time limit!
（今吉）ゾーンは100％の力を
発揮する反面 反動も大きい
While the Zone allows an athlete to exhibit 100% of his power,
the recoil is significant.
だが 何で青峰だけ…
But why only Aomine?
An ace carrying his teammates' wishes cannot lose.
（黒子(くろこ)）
みんなの想いを背負ったエースは
絶対に負けない
I believe in Kagami.
信じてますから
火神君を
Don't be ridiculous.
（青峰）ざけんな！
That can't make me...
そんなことでオレが…
Aomine, you're strong.
（火神）青峰… オマエは強(つえ)えよ
１対１なら マジで勝てなかった
If this were a one-on-one, I would have lost.
I've already exceeded my time limit too.
タイムリミットなんて
オレだって とっくにきてた
But the reason I can keep on fighting is I have support.
それでも まだ戦えるのは…
支えがあるからだ
I'm fighting with more than one man's strength!
１人分の力じゃねえんだよ！
For all the guys...
（火神）みんなのために…
（青峰）フンッ！
（火神）ぜってえ 勝つ！！
I will win!
（日向）んんっ！
（伊月(いづき)）ふっ！
（桜井･若松(わかまつ)）
くっ… ハァ… ハァ…
Seirin
Touou
（誠凛(せいりん)選手たち）よっしゃあああ！
Yeah!
We're one point behind!
１点差だ！
（降旗）でも残り30秒…
But there are only 30 seconds left.
We can do it! I know we can!
（土田）いける！ 絶対にいける！
（原澤）
すみません タイムアウトを
Excuse me.
I'd like to call a time out.
Are you okay, Aomine?
（諏佐）大丈夫か 青峰？
Don't touch me.
（青峰）触んな
I just tripped.
（青峰）
ちょっとつまずいただけだろうが
Don't get in my way.
邪魔すんなよ
いいとこなんだからよぉ
This is the best part.
Things are just getting hyped up.
こっからだろうが
一番テンション上がんのは…
I'm sorry.
すみません やはり
タイムアウトはいいです
We don't need a time out after all.
Harasawa's not calling a time out.
（中谷(なかたに)）
原澤はタイムアウトを取らんな
Even if he calls one now...
ここは一度 取っても…
いや 取るべき場面だろう
No, he should be calling one now.
It's hard to say.
（景虎(かげとら)）さあな
There are some things you have to experience to understand.
まっ 現場にしか分からねえ
空気っつうもんも あるからな
For better or for worse,
良くも悪くも タイムアウトを
取れば 流れが一度切れる
if he calls a time out, it'll disrupt the flow of the game.
Sometimes you make that call after seeing the look in your players' eyes.
選手の目を見て
そういう判断する時も あんだろ
There are times when you prioritize emotion over strategy.
戦略より 気持ちを優先する時がよ
Come on!
１本！！
死んでも止めるぞぉ！！
Let's stop this shot, even if it kills us!
Amazing.
すげぇ…
That's some good defense.
いいディフェンスだ
（部員たち）
ディーフェンス ディーフェンス！
Defense! Defense! Defense!
We're fully aware of that.
（今吉）そんなん 百も承知や
ほなら こっちも
やることは １つ…
There's only one thing for us to do.
いまさら裏も表もないで
There are no more tricks left to play.
But Aomine is still the strongest!
（今吉）それでも最強は 青峰や
フン！
He stopped him!
（福田(ふくだ)）止めたあ！
よおし 火神ぃ！
袋小路だ！
Yeah, Kagami!
He's cornered!
くっ… フンッ！
Crap!
（火神）しまった！
（黒子）あっ！
（木吉(きよし)）んっ…
Impossible.
（伊月）そんな… ここにきて
まだそんなシュートが 打てんのか
He can still make shots like that?
Damn it.
（日向）くそ… バケモンめ…
He's a monster.
（青峰）
ふっ 負けるかよ…
I won't lose.
A battle's no fun if you don't win.
勝負ってのは 勝たなきゃ
何も面白くねえんだよ
（観客たちの歓声）
（観客１）うわっ！ 決めた！
He made the shot!
（観客２）桐皇(とうおう) とどめの一撃！
Touou struck the killing blow!
Seirin
Touou
（観客３）
この３点差は キツすぎる！
Seirin
Touou
This three point difference is too much!
Seirin
Touou
This isn't good. There's no time left.
やべえぞ 時間がもう…
Seirin doesn't have the strength left to play in overtime.
（笠松）もはや誠凛に
延長を戦う力は 残ってねえ
スリーポイントで
同点じゃダメだ
Tying the score with a three-pointer isn't good enough.
They need two more shots.
どうしても あと２本いる
If things end like this, nothing will have changed.
（黄瀬）このまま終わったら…
結局 前と一緒じゃないっスか
I don't want to see that happen.
そんなん 見たか ねえんスよ！
勝てぇ 誠凛！！
Win, Seirin!
Don't give up!
絶対 諦めんじゃねぇー！
だあっ 時間がないっ！
There's no time!
Do something...
何とか… 何とかしてくれぇ！
Please do something!
It's coming down to the wire.
（日向）いよいよ ヤベェぜ…
こうなったら
イチかバチか やるしかねぇ
I need to take a chance.
Barrier Jumper!
バリアジャンパー！
Misdirection Overflow!
（黒子）ミスディレクション･
オーバーフロー！
（日向）ダメか… ちくしょう
It won't work.
Damn it.
His Overflow has stopped working.
ここにきて
オーバーフローも切れた…
正真正銘 黒子は限界だ…！
Kuroko is truly at his limit.
（火神）キャプテン！
（日向）あっ！
Captain!
（日向）火神！ うっ！
Kagami!
決めてくれ！！ 火神！！
Make it, Kagami!
（火神）ヤベェ…
このダンクは止められる
Crap.
He's going to stop the dunk.
どうすりゃいいんだ くそぉ！！
What should I do?
Damn it!
（黒子）火神君！
（火神）はっ！
Kagami!
（緑間）まさか“空中戦なら
勝てる”などと思ってないだろうな
Don't tell me you believe you can fight him in the air.
その答えでは まだ半分だ
That is only half the answer.
I'll become able to move at will in the air!
（火神）オレは
空中で自在に動けるようになる！
えいっ！
（青峰）パス… だと！？
A pass?
He finally conquered his assignment from the summer
（リコ）最後の最後で
夏からの課題を 克服した！
at the very last second.
Go!
（部員たち）いっけぇー！
No, you don't!
（若松）させるかっ！！
ki
mi
ga
no
zo
mu
no
na
ra
ba
ka
mi
tsu
i
te
mo
i
If this is what you want, go ahead and bare your fangs.
ki
mi
ga
no
zo
mu
no
na
ra
ba
ka
mi
tsu
i
te
mo
i
They're stronger than us,
（木吉）パワーでは負けている
ん… だが 逆転のチャンスを
つくるには やるしかない！
but it's the only way to create an opportunity for a comeback!
wa
na
ku
bu
ru
u
na
ki
mo
chi
hi
ki
ka
e
ni
shi
te
Let them take the place of these fragile blue feelings.
wananaku buruu na kimochi hikikae ni shite
A fake?
（若松）フェイク！？
テメェ まさか…！
Is this bastard...
a
se
ru
na
my
bright
est
heart
Hold steady, my brightest heart...
a
se
ru
na
my
bright
est
heart
We've shared joy and sorrow.
ku
ra
wo
to
mo
ni
shi
te
ki
ta
mo
u
hi
to
ri
ga
se
na
ka
go
shi
de
su
ma
i
ru
You're the one who's always got my back with a smile.
mou hitori ga senaka goshi de sumairu
"Don't worry," I'll try to believe those words.
don't
wo
rry
na
n
te
shi
n
ji
te
mi
ta
i
don't
wo
rry
na
n
te
shi
n
ji
te
mi
ta
i
（審判）ディフェンス！
プッシング 黒６番！
Defense! Pushing!
Black No. 6! Basket counts!
バスケットカウント ワンスロー！
de
ki
ru
no
wa
mo
u
shi
t
te
ru
ze
ka
t
te
ru
ze
I already know we can do this. I know we can win.
de
ki
ru
no
wa
mo
u
shi
t
te
ru
ze
ka
t
te
ru
ze
And one!
All right!
（伊月･日向）
うおっしゃあああ！
'Cause he and I are one and the same.
da
t
te
a
i
tsu
wa
o
re
ji
shi
n
Let
me
high
er!
Get
me
high
er!
You're amazing, Teppei.
（リコ）すごいわ 鉄平(てっぺい)
The fire inside me is burning bright.
mo
e
ru
mi
no
a
tsu
sa
wa
But the truly surprising thing was Kagami's assist.
それより さらに
驚かされたのは—
Even on this day like any other
na
n
to
na
ku
no
kyo
u
de
mo
we're burnin' up, love, and believe.
burn
in'
up,
we
love
shi
n
ji
te
火神君のアシスト！
In order to improve himself in the air, he'd been practicing
元々 夏から
彼は空中戦を向上させるため—
Rock
me,
ba
by.
Show
me
ba
by.
Let's see more of what we can do.
mi
se
te
ku
re
mo
t
to
左手のハンドリングを
ずっと練習していた
his left-handed handling since the summer.
The way you and I are gonna create
o
re
to
ki
mi
to
de
tsu
ku
ri
a
ge
ru
n
da
ゾーンに入っていたとはいえ—
He may have been in the Zone,
but I just can't believe he made it happen at the very last second.
この土壇場で モノにするなんて…
de
n
se
tsu
wo
o
ther
self
our legendary other selves.
densetsu wo other self
（火神）ハァ… ハァ…
I can't believe he passed there.
（青峰）あのタイミングで
まさかパスとはよ
Kuroko's
I
Basketball
やってくれんじゃねーか
Not bad.
Seirin
Touou
They're one point behind.
Seirin
Touou
（黄瀬）１点差…
Seirin
Touou
And they drew a defensive foul.
しかも ディフェンスファウルだ
フリースローが もう１本
They've got another free throw.
There are five seconds left.
Seirin
Touou
（高尾）残り５秒…
If they make this, they'll be tied.
決めれば同点… 延長か
The game will go into overtime.
That path will only lead to their demise.
だが それでは
死路に向かうことになる
Seirin needs to make a comeback here to win.
誠凛が勝つには
ここで逆転するしかない
To do that...
そのためにも…
It's obvious what they're going to go.
（今吉）やることは決まっとる
There's only one thing they can do now.
ここからのシナリオは
もう １つしかない
They won't make this free throw.
このフリースローは 必ず外れる
No, they'll make sure it'll miss.
いや… 外してくるはずや
（日向）それを奪って 決める
Then we'll steal the ball and score.
It's the only way to win.
勝つ方法は それしかねえ
We've given everything we have and are at our limit,
こっちは もう万策出しきって
ギリギリなのに引き換え—
向こうは 体力も
ベンチの層の厚さも 余力がある
but they've got stamina and bench players to spare.
Our loss is certain in an overtime game.
同点延長じゃ 確実に負けだ
However, with Kiyoshi shooting, Kagami and I will be rebounding.
だが シューターが木吉ってことは
セットするのは オレと 火神だ
Naturally, I'll go for the ball with everything I have.
オレも当然 全力で取りに行く
それでも…
可能性があるとしたら 火神—
But...
If anyone has a chance, it's you, Kagami.
オマエしかいねえ
行くぞ
Let's go.
This is our last play.
これがラストプレーだ
A battle for the rebound!
リバウンド勝負！
One shot!
（審判）ワンショット！
（火神）うぐっ！
（諏佐･若松）ぬおっ！！
（さつき）ああっ！
（原澤）何っ！？
What?!
（火神）ぬうっ！
（火神）はっ…
（青峰）おらっ！
フリーだ！ そのまま決められる！
He's wide open!
He can take it to the basket!
We've won!
（桜井）ウチの勝ちだ！
（今吉）なっ！ ちょお 待てや
Wait a minute!
何で… 何で オマエが
そんなとこ おんねん
What...
What are you doing there?!
ハァ ハァ…
Kuroko!
（今吉）黒子！
Even though I'm on his team,
（今吉）味方のワシらでさえ
一瞬 火神に取られた思うて—
I thought Kagami had the ball for a moment
and was a few seconds late to move after Aomine knocked the ball away.
青峰が はじいてから
動き出すまでに—
コンマ何秒か遅れた
I can't believe he moved faster than me.
それより動き出しが
早いやなんて…
You're kidding me.
あり得へん…
Did he believe not in Kagami, but in Aomine instead?!
火神でなく… 青峰のほうを
信じたっちゅうんか！？
No, that's not quite right.
いいえ 少し違います
I believed in them both.
ボクが信じたのは両方です
However, there's only one person I believe will make the final shot!
でも 最後に決めてくれると
信じてるのは１人だけだ！
Kagami!
火神君！ フンッ！
（火神･青峰）えいっ！
（火神）ええぃっ！
Go, Kagami!
（部員たち）
いけえー！！ 火神！！
それに 青峰君より
すごい人なんて すぐ現れますよ
Besides, I'm sure you'll meet someone more amazing than yourself soon.
Time's up!
Seirin
Touou
（審判）タイムアップ！
（青峰）負け…
I...
lost?
I see...
そうか…
I lost.
負けたのか…
I...
オレは
（審判）整列！
Line up!
ん… ハァ…
Kuroko!
黒子！？
（火神）んっ… 大丈夫かよ んん
Are you okay?
Sheesh.
（青峰）ったく 支えてもらって
立ってるのが やっとかよ
You can barely stand with support.
No one can tell who won now.
これじゃ どっちが勝ったか
分からねえじゃねーか
けど それでよかったのかも
しんねえな
But maybe that was for the best.
The reason I lost was that difference.
結局 敗因は—
その差だったってこと…
だからな
Why are you acting like it's all over?
（火神）何 もう全部
終わったような顔してんだよ
まだ 始まったばっかだろーが
Things are just getting started.
Let's play again.
また やろーぜ
受けてやるからよ
I'll take you on.
クッ ぬかせ バカ
Shut up, idiot.
Aomine.
青峰君
Your basketball cannot win.
（青峰）
オマエのバスケじゃ 勝てねえよ
You win, Tetsu.
オマエの勝ちだ テツ
（黒子）１つ いいですか？
（青峰）ん？
Can I ask you for a favor?
You still haven't returned my fist bump.
（黒子）あの時の拳を
まだ合わせてません
What?!
Who cares about that?
いーじゃねえか そんなもん！
No.
（黒子）嫌です
Try putting yourself in the shoes of the ignored.
だいたい シカトされた側の
身にも なってください
Fine.
分かったよ ただし—
This is
the last time though.
これっきりだ
Next time, I'll win.
（青峰）次は勝つからな
（黒子）はい
Okay.
kasunda mirai wo kirisaku you ni terasu hikari
Like a shining light that cuts through the hazy future,
musuu no kanousei wo motome
I chase after unlimited possibilities.
Gotta open my eyes
Seirin High wins with a score of 101 to 100!
（審判）１０１対１００で
誠凛高校の勝ち！ 礼！
Bow!
Thanks for the game!
（選手たち）
ありがとうございました！
Wake up sabitsuita me ni hi wo tomose
Wake up, light a fire in your tired eyes.
Get up kusubutteru baai ja nainda zettai
Get up! Now's definitely not the time to let it smoulder.
youi sareta risou nante iranai
You don't need to have some big dream.
yuragu koto no nai ishi to
Just an unwavering spirit,
mikansei na chizu de ii kara
and an unfinished map is enough.
asu wo tsukame kono te de
Hold on to tomorrow with these hands!
detarame na rizumu de nurikaete iku kako ni
Regretting a past that's being overwritten by a nonsensical rhythm...
koukai hitotsu arienai daro
That's not possible, right?
ari no mama no biito de kurikaeshite iku genzei wo
I'll rewrite things with the true beat now,
kasaneta mirai kagayaku you ni
and create a sparkling future.
kizami konda sonzai wo kesshou toshite
Your existence is etched as a crystal.
Keep it in my story
Touou Academy
Dressing Room
It's time for the third-years to retire.
Touou Academy
Dressing Room
（今吉）ちゅーわけで
ワシら３年は これで引退や
Touou Academy
Dressing Room
Thanks for everything up until now.
今までありがとうな
Wakamatsu will be the new captain.
新主将は 若松にやってもらう
Make us proud.
よろしゅう頼むわ
Wait...
What?!
You'll be fine.
大丈夫 こういうのは
習うより慣れろや
It can't be taught. You'll get used to it.
あ いや そうじゃなくて…
That's not the problem.
切り替え 早すぎっつーか…
You changed subjects so quickly.
What are you talking about?
何言うてんねん
一回戦負けやで？
We lost our first game.
悲しんどるヒマあったら
帰って 練習せえや
If you've got time to be sad, go home and practice.
（桜井）あっ！ 目が…
Their eyes...
当たり前だ 先輩たちは３年…
It's only natural.
They're third-years.
これが最後の大会だったんだ
This was their last tournament.
There's no way they wouldn't feel something.
何も感じないわけ あるもんか…！
But I won't be able to handle Aomine the way you do, Imayoshi.
けど オレ
今吉さんみたく 青峰と—
やってけねーっスよ 絶対
フッ 青峰は嫌いか？
Do you hate Aomine?
Yeah, I do.
嫌いっス
Then who do you think is most suited to being this team's ace?
（今吉）じゃあ今—
このチームで誰が一番
エースにふさわしいと思うとる？
Aomine.
青峰っス
As long as you understand that, you'll be fine.
そんだけ分かっとれば 大丈夫や
何も心配してへんで ワシは
I'm not worried.
あっ そーいや その青峰は？
Speaking of which, where's Aomine?
He's missing, and Momoi's looking for him.
あっ… 行方不明で…
桃井(ももい)さんが捜してます
（若松）ムッ あのガキゃあ！
That brat!
（青峰）ハァ…
I found you.
（さつき）あ〜 見つけたあ
（青峰）あ？
（さつき）もう すぐ１人で
どっか行っちゃわないでよぉ
Don't go wandering off by yourself.
Come on. Let's go back to the rest of the team.
ほら みんなのとこ 早く戻ろ？
さつき 明日ヒマか？
Satsuki, are you free tomorrow?
What? Well, yeah.
えっ？ そりゃあ…
Will you go shopping with me?
（青峰）
買い物 付き合ってくんね？
What?
Sure, I guess.
いやっ… いいけど…
What? Where did that come from?
えっ 何？ 急に
バッシュ 新しいの欲しいんだよ
I want new basketball shoes.
ああ… 練習してえ
I want to practice.
フッ いいよっ！
Sure. Let's go, Dai.
行こっか 大(だい)ちゃん！
けど ご飯 おごってね
But you have to buy me dinner though.
What?!
Seirin High
Dressing Room
（降旗）あれ？ 帰り支度
まだなんですか？
Huh? We're not ready to go yet?
Seirin High
Dressing Room
いやあ… 私も早く
帰りたいんだけど…
Yeah, I want to leave too, but...
もうちょっとだけ
そっとしといて あげましょ
Let's leave them be for a little longer.
What?
Good work, boys.
（リコ）おつかれさま
Next Episode
（小金井）お邪魔しま〜す
…って部屋 広っ！！
Excuse me...
This place is huge!
But there's nothing in here.
でも 何もねえな
All I do is eat and sleep here.
（火神）基本 メシ食って
寝るだけなんで
（小金井）ん… とりあえず
トイレ貸して〜
Let me use your bathroom.
（火神）あっちっス
（小金井）ええと… ここか！
It's over there.
Is this it?
A b-b-blonde?!
Episode
Tell Me
って… きき… 金髪！？